A Guide to the Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) records FA476
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Files and Grants, 1
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park (Box 57)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park (Box 57)
  - Legal (Box 57)
  - Legal (Box 57)
  - A report and proposal on filing (Box 57)
  - Organization and Staffing of Activities in Suite 5125 (Box 57)
  - Merger (Box 57)
  - Memoranda I (Box 57)
  - Memoranda II (Box 57)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1981 (Box 57)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1980 (Box 57)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1979 (Box 57)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1978 (Box 57)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1977 (Box 57)
  - Meetings/Minutes, 1976 (Box 57)
  - Minutes/Meetings - Annual Meeting - Travel Arrangements, 1976 (Box 57)
  - Meetings/Minutes, 1975 (Box 57)
  - Meetings/Minutes, 1974 (Box 57)
  - Meetings/Minutes, 1973 (Box 57)
  - Meetings/Minutes, 1972 (Box 57)
  - Museum of the American Indian, NYC (Box 57)
  - Office Equipment (Box 57)
  - Museum of the American Indian, NYC (Box 57)
  - National Park Foundation (Box 57)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission (Box 57)
  - Peregrine, Smith Inc. (Box 57)
  - Public Benefit Corporation (Box 57)
  - Requests - A-AM (Box 58)
  - Requests - A-B (Box 58)
  - Requests - AN-B (Box 58)
  - Requests - CA-CO (Box 58)
  - Requests - CR-D (Box 58)
  - Requests - C-E (Box 58)
  - Requests - E (Box 58)
  - Requests - F-G (Box 58)
  - Requests - H-I-J (Box 58)
  - Requests - F-J (Box 58)
  - Requests - K-L (Box 58)
  - Requests - K-L (Box 58)
  - Requests - M (Box 58)
  - Requests - M (Box 58)
  - Requests - N (Box 58)
  - Requests - N (Box 58)
  - Incorporation (Box 59)
  - Requests - O-R (Box 59)
  - Requests - O-P-Q (Box 59)
  - Requests - R (Box 59)
  - Requests - S (Box 59)
  - Requests - T (Box 59)
  - Requests - T-U (Box 59)
  - Requests - V-W (Box 59)
  - Requests - X-Y-Z (Box 59)
  - Requests - U-Z (Box 59)
  - St. John's Hospital (Box 59)
  - Save the Redwoods League, 2 folders. (Box 59)
  - St. John, V.I. - Sale of Land (Box 59)
  - Taxes (Box 59)
  - Teton Science School (Box 59)
  - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service (Box 60)
  - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service (Box 60)
  - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - Matching Funds (Box 60)
  - Evaluation of the Historical and Present Position of Grand Teton Lodge Company and Caneel Bay Plantation, Inc., 1978 (Box 60)
  - National Park Service - Concessions (Box 60)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park (Box 60)
  - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park A-Z, 1977-1981 (Box 60)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park- A-Z (Box 60)
  - NPS - Grand Teton National Park - Boundary and Land Use Study (Box 60)
  - Grand Teton National Park- Clippings (Box 60)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service- Grand Teton National Park - Clippings (Box 60)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Hole Airport - A-Z (Box 60)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Hole Airport - A-Z (Box 60)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Hole Airport, 1977-1981 (Box 60)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Hole Airport, 1976 (Box 61)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Hole Airport, 1975 (Box 61)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Hole Airport, 1974 (Box 61)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Hole Airport, 1973 (Box 61)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Hole Airport, 1971-1972 (Box 61)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Hole Airport - Clippings (Box 61)
  - Jackson Hole Airport - Clippings (Box 61)
  - USG - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Centennial Commission (Box 61)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park - Teton Science School (Box 61)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Virgin Islands National Park (Box 61)
  - United States Government - Department of the Interior - Virgin Islands National Park (Box 61)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Virgin Islands National Park - A-Z (Box 61)
  - Virgin Islands National Park - A-Z (Box 61)
  - Virgin Islands National Park - Clippings (Box 61)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Virgin Islands National Park - Clippings (Box 61)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Virgin Islands National Park - Jetport (Box 61)
  - United States Government (USG) - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Foundation - Visitor Facilities Fund (Box 62)
  - USG - Dept. of the Interior - National Park Service - Virgin Islands National Park - Printed Material (Box 62)
  - Vermont (Box 62)
  - Virgin Islands Government (Box 62)
  - Izaak Walter League of America (Box 62)
  - Whistling Cay Customs House (Box 62)
  - World Wildlife Fund - U.S. (Box 62)
  - Wyoming Annual Report (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - General Correspondence - A-M (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - General Correspondence - N-Z (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - General Correspondence (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay - A-H (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay - I-Z (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Board of Trustees (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Board of Trustees (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay - Contributions (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Articles/Clippings (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Employees (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation- Employees (Box 62)
  - Caneel Bay - Finances, 1981 (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay - Finances, 1980 (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay - Finances, 1979 (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Finances, 1977-1978 (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Finances (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Legal (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Legal (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Minutes/Meetings (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay Inc. - Board of Directors Meeting, 1981 (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Meetings/Minutes (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Printed Material (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - Printed Material (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay - Solar Energy (Projects, Hot Water) (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay - USG Dept. of Interior - National Park Service (Box 63)
  - Caneel Bay - National Park Service - Sale (Box 63)
  - Evaluation of the Historical and Present Position of Grand Teton Lodge Company and Caneel Bay Plantation, Inc., 1978 (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - A-Z (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - General Correspondence (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - General Correspondence - A-M (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - General Correspondence - N-Z (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - Board of Trustees (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - Board of Trustees (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - Clippings (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - Fairways Estates (Wort Property) (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. and Subsidiaries - Report on Examination, 1976; 2 copies. (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. and Subsidiaries - Report on Examination, 1975 (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. and Subsidiaries - Financial Statements and Supplementary Information, 1974 (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. and Subsidiaries - Financial Statements and Supplementary Information, 1973 (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - Financial Statements and Supplementary Information, 1972 (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - Financial Statements, 1971 (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - Finances (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Finances (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Jackson Hole Golf and Tennis Club (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Jackson Hole Golf and Tennis Estates (Box 64)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Jackson Hole Golf and Tennis Club (Box 64)
  - Environmental Impact Assessment Report - Jackson Hole Airport - Volume I (Box 65)
  - Environmental Impact Assessment Report - Jackson Hole Airport - Volume III Appendices (Box 65)
  - Airport Master Plan Report - Jackson Hole Airport, 1976 July (Box 65)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Meetings/Minutes (Box 65)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Meetings/Minutes (Box 65)
  - Meeting Minutes of the Annual Board Meeting, 1980 (Box 65)
  - Agenda for - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - Meeting of Board of Directors, 1980; 3 copies (Box 65)
  - Agenda for - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - Meeting of Board of Directors, 1979 (Box 65)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - Minutes/Meetings (Box 65)
  - Notebooks, 2 (Box 65)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. - Sale (Box 65)
  - PR - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Brochures and Tariffs, 1961 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Brochures and Tariffs, 1960 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Brochures and Tariffs - through 1957 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Colter Bay Dedication, 1959 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Colter Bay - Maps (Trailer Area), 1956 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Colter Bay - Maps - Site Plan and Caption, 1956 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - National Park Service, Pamphlets, Etc. (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Menus (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Colter Bay Dedication, 1957 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Jackson Lake Lodge Opening, 1955 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Colter Bay General - through 1957 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Jenny Lake Lodge Re-Opening, 1958 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Jackson Lake Lodge - Opening - Speeches, 1955 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Questionnaire, 1956 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Questionnaire, 1957 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Questionnaire, 1958 (Box 66)
  - A Development Program for the Grand Teton Lodges (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Questions (Ten Most Frequently Asked), 1956 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Post Cards (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Grand Teton National Park (Property Purchase) - thru 1957 (Box 66)
  - GTLCO - Grand Teton National Park - Property Purchase - Appraisals, Maps, etc. (Box 66)
  - Report on Private Land Situation - Grand Teton National Park (Box 66)
  - Market Value of Caneel Bay (Box 67)
  - Caneel - Moses Report (Box 67)
  - Report on Proposal to Establish the Island of St. John as a National Park or Monument, 2 folders. (Box 67)
  - Caneel - National Park Service - General Correspondence - thru 1957 (Box 67)
  - GTLCO - Transportation - Jackson Hole Airport, 1958 (Box 67)
  - GTLCO - Grand Teton National Park - Properties - "Craighead Brothers" (Box 67)
  - Caneel - Virgin Islands National Park - Park Project - Bill - House Bill, 1955-1956 (Box 67)
  - Caneel - Virgin Islands National Park - Park Project - Bill - Senate Bill Hearings, 1955-1956 (Box 67)
  - Caneel - Virgin Islands National Park - Park Project - Bill, 1958 (Box 67)
  - Caneel - Virgin Islands National Park - Park Project - Bill, 1957 (Box 67)
  - Caneel - Virgin Islands National Park - Park Project - Bill - General, 1955-1956 (Box 67)
  - Dorado - Boats - Wayfarer - Plans, Prints, Photos, Etc. (Box 67)
  - Dorado - Properties - Livingston, Clara - through 1954 (Box 67)
  - Dorado - Subdivision - Dorado Beach Estates - House Plans (Box 67)
  - Dorado - Properties - Livingston, Clara, 1955 (Box 67)
  - Dorado - Properties - Livingston, Clara, 1956 (Box 67)
  - A Study of Teton County and the town of Jackson, State of Wyoming - Leslie A. Miller, 1926-1946 (Box 67)
  - Abercrombie Property (National Park Service) (Box 68)
  - Deed of Trust between JHPI and the Taconic State Park Commission (Box 68)
  - Land Acquisition - Vermont (Box 68)
  - Land St. John, Virgin Islands (Four Estates) (Box 68)
  - Indian Collection (Gamer and Cummings) (Box 68)
  - Indian Collection (Vernon) (Box 68)
  - Indian Collection (Box 68)
  - Real Estate, Washington D.C. - (Corr Property) (Box 68)
  - Oral History - Columbia University (Mason Agreement) (Box 68)
  - Pledges - Rockefeller Brothers Fund (Box 68)
  - Pledges - Rockefeller, David (Box 68)
  - Pledges - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Box 68)
  - Pledges (Miscellaneous) (Box 68)
  - Pledges - National Park Service (Box 68)
  - Save the Redwoods League (Box 68)
  - Stock Subscription to Grand Teton Lodge Co., 1960-1961 (Box 68)
  - Stock Subscription to Grand Teton Lodge Co., 1956-1959 (Box 68)
  - "Patman Report" (Box 68)
  - "Patman Report" (Box 68)
  - Patman - Additional Information, 1967 (Box 68)
  - Patman - Additional Information, 1965-1966 (Box 68)
  - Audit Worksheets and Reports/Agenda re: Trustee Meeting, 1976 (Box 68)
  - Credit Memorandum, 1976 (Box 68)
  - Journal Entries, 1976 (Box 68)
  - Grants Paid, 1976 (Box 68)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank Statements, 1976 (Box 68)
  - New York State - Form NYCF-2 (Annual Report of Charitable Organizations), 1966-1969 (Box 69)
  - JHPI - Form 990-PF and 990-AR, 1974 (Box 69)
  - JHPI - Form 990-PF and 990-AR, 1973 (Box 69)
  - JHPI - 990-PF and 990-AR( Also for Virgin Islands), 1972 (Box 69)
  - JHPI - Form 990-PF and 990-AR, 1971 (Box 69)
  - JHPI - Form 990, 4720, and 990 AR, 1970 (Box 69)
  - JHPI - Form 990-A, 1968-1969 (Box 69)
  - JHPI - Form 990-A, 1966-1967 (Box 69)
  - JHPI - Form 990-A, 1964-1965 (Box 69)
  - JHPI - Form 990-A, 1962-1963 (Box 69)
  - JHPI - Form 990-A, 1959-1961 (Box 69)
  - JHPI - Form 990-A, 1954-1958 (Box 69)
  - Allston Boyer - Reservations - West Indies Trips, 1954 (Box 70)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Treasurer's F.- Income Tax Returns, 1952-1954 (Box 70)
  - Caneel Bay - Purchase, 1952 (Box 70)
  - Caneel Bay - Taxation, 1952-1954 (Box 70)
  - Report on Engineering Problems at St. John (Box 70)
  - Report on Caneel Bay Plantation Inc. - Caneel Bay, St. John, Virgin Islands (Box 70)
  - Caneel Bay - Employees (Box 70)
  - Caneel Bay Opening, 1956 (Box 70)
  - Caneel Bay Plantations (Box 70)
  - Caneel Bay- La Farge- Const.- Env. #2 (Box 70)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation, 1953-1955 (Box 70)
  - Caneel Bay Plantation - C.C. Layton, 1953-1954 (Box 70)
  - 1952-1954 (Box 71)
  - Finance Committee, 1955 February 3 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1955 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1956 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1957 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1958 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1959 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1960 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1961 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1962 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1963 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1964 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1965 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1966 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1973 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1974 (Box 71)
  - Agendas, Executive Committee and Annual Meeting materials, 1975 (Box 71)
  - "A-M" (Box 72)
  - "N-Z" (Box 72)
  - Adirondack Land Trust (Box 72)
  - American Conservation Association (Box 72)
  - American Wilderness Alliance (Box 72)
  - American Wildlands (Box 72)
  - Horace M. Albright Memorial (Box 72)
  - Carlisle H. Humelsine Memorial (Box 72)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 72)
  - CSX - Sale of Grand Teton Lodge Co. and Caneel Bay Inc., 1986 (Box 73)
  - CSX - Sale of Grand Teton Lodge Co. and Caneel Bay Inc., 1986 (Box 73)
  - JHPI- CSX- Sale of Grand Teton Lodge Co. and Caneel Bay Inc.- Env. #1- 1986 (Box 73)
  - Caneel Bay, inc. (Box 73)
  - Defenders of Wildlife (Box 73)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary (Box 73)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Book (Box 73)
  - The Tetons and the Yellowstone (Box 73)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Book - George D. Taylor Jr. Material (Box 73)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Book - George D. Taylor Jr. Material (Box 73)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Book - George D. Taylor Jr. Material (Box 73)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Slides, 5 binders. (Box 74)
  - JHPI - 50tn Anniversary Book - Grand Teton Photos (Needham and Grohmann) (Box 75)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Background Material - Book (Box 75)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Background Material - Book (Box 75)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Background Material - Book (Box 75)
  - Finances (Box 76)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Co. (Box 76)
  - Grand Teton Natural History Association (Box 76)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition (Box 76)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition (Box 76)
  - Historic Hudson Valley (Box 76)
  - Hudson River Project (Box 76)
  - Hudson River Project (Box 76)
  - Hudson River Valley Meeting, 1987 October 21 (Box 77)
  - Hudson River Project (Box 77)
  - Hudson River Project (Box 77)
  - Hudson River Project (Box 77)
  - Hudson River Project, 1991 (Box 77)
    Filed as Received
  - Hudson River Project, 1989 (Box 77)
  - Hudson River Project, 1988 (Box 77)
  - Hudson River Project, 1987 (Box 77)
  - International Wilderness Leadership Foundation (Box 78)
  - Jackson Hole Alliance for Responsible Planniog (Box 78)
  - Jackson Hole Land Trust (Box 78)
  - Meetings, 1991 (Box 78)
  - Meetings, 1990 (Box 78)
  - Annual Meetings of the Board - Minutes (Copies), 1940-1989 (Box 78)
  - Meetings, 1989 (Box 78)
  - Meetings, 1988 (Box 78)
  - Meetings, 1987 (Box 78)
  - Meetings, 1986 (Box 79)
  - Montana and Reliance (Box 79)
  - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation (Box 79)
  - National Maritime Historical Society (Box 79)
  - National Wildlife Federation (Box 79)
  - Nature Conservancy (Box 79)
  - New York State (Box 79)
  - New York State Office of Parks - Recreation and Historic Preservation (Box 79)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission (Box 79)
  - Printed Material (Box 79)
  - Safari Club International (Box 79)
  - Saugerties Lighthouse Conservancy (Box 79)
  - Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund, Inc. (Box 79)
  - Sleepy Hollow Restorations (Box 79)
  - Student Conservation Association (Box 79)
  - USG - Department of the Interior - National Park Service (Box 80)
  - Teton Science School (Box 80)
  - Trust for Public Land (Box 80)
  - National Park Service - 75th Anniversary (Box 80)
  - National Park Foundation (Box 80)
  - Grand Teton National Park (Box 80)
  - Department of the Interior - National Parks Service - Virgin Island National Park (Box 80)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Airport (Box 80)
  - The University of Vermont - Department of Botany (Box 80)
  - Izaak Walton League of America, Inc. (Box 80)
  - The Western Foundation (Box 80)
  - Wildlife Habitat Enhancement Council (Box 80)
  - Year 2000 (Box 80)
  - Zion Natural History Association (Box 80)
  - "A-L" (Box 81)
  - "M-Z" (Box 81)
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks (Box 81)
  - American Academy for Parks and Recreation Administration (Box 81)
  - American Conservation Association (Box 81)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 81)
  - British Virgin Islands National Parks Trust (Box 81)
  - California State Parks Foundation (Box 81)
  - Finances (Box 81)
  - Finances / Gifts (Box 81)
  - Governor's Environment 2000 Conference (Box 81)
  - Grand Teton Natural History Association (Box 81)
  - Greater Yellowstone Coalition (Box 81)
  - History (Box 81)
  - Hudson River Project, 1986 (Box 81)
  - Hudson River Project, 1985 (Box 81)
  - Hudson River Project, 1984 (Box 81)
  - Hudson River Project, 1981-1983 (Box 82)
  - Hudson River Project, 1984, 1986; 10 folders (Box 82)
    General note
    Filed as received from GRL's Office.
  - Hudson River Project - GRL Env., 1983; 2 folders. (Box 83)
  - Hudson River Project - Dovel, William L., 2 folders. (Box 83)
  - Inform, Inc. (Box 84)
  - Island Resources Foundation (Box 84)
  - Jackson Hole Land Trust (Box 84)
  - Jackson Hole Alliance for Responsible Planning (Box 84)
  - Jackson Hole Museum Foundation, Inc. (Box 84)
  - Manitoga, Inc. (Box 84)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1986 (Box 84)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1985 (Box 84)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1984 (Box 84)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1983 (Box 84)
  - Minutes/Meetings, 1982 (Box 84)
  - Montana Land Reliance (Box 85)
  - National Maritime Historical Society (Box 85)
  - National Park Foundation (Box 85)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council (Box 85)
  - New York State - Natural Heritage Trust (Box 85)
  - New York State - Office of Parks, Recreation and Historic Preservation (Box 85)
  - New York Zoological Society (Box 85)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission (Box 85)
  - Resources for the Future (Box 85)
  - Safari Club International Conversation Fund (Box 85)
  - School for Field Studies (Box 85)
  - Sleepy Hollow Restorations (Box 85)
  - South Street Seaport Museum (Box 85)
  - Teton Science School (Box 85)
  - National Park Service - Grand Teton National Park, A-Z (Box 85)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Airport, 1982 (Box 85)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Airport, 1983 (Box 85)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Airport, 1984-1985 (Box 85)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Airport, 1982 (Box 86)
  - Grand Teton National Park - Jackson Airport, 1980 (Box 86)
  - United States Government - President's Commission on Americans Outdoors (Box 86)
  - University of Vermont - Department of Botany (Box 86)
  - Izaak Walton League of America, Inc. (Box 86)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. (Box 86)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc., A-C (Box 86)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc., D-G (Box 86)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc., H-J (Box 86)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc., K-M (Box 86)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc., N-R (Box 86)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc., S-Z (Box 86)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Appraisal (Box 86)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Allen Williams Company (Box 86)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Documents (Box 87)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Caribbean Conservation Association (Box 87)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Cinammon Bay (Box 87)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Finances, 1985 (Box 87)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Finances, 1984 (Box 87)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Finances, 1983 (Box 87)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Finances, 1982 (Box 87)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Minutes/Meetings (Box 87)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - First Centrum Corporation (Box 87)
  - Caneel Bay - USG - Dept. of the Interior - NPS Connecticut General Life (Box 88)
  - Caneel Bay - USG - Dept. of the Interior - NPS Legal (Box 88)
  - Untitled (Box 88)
  - Caneel Bay - USG - Dept. of the Interior - NPS Land Gift (Box 88)
  - Caneel Bay - USG - Dept. of the Interior - NPS - "A-Z" (Box 88)
  - Caneel Bay - USG - Dept. of the Interior - NPS Land Gift - Press Releases (Box 88)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - "A-M" (Box 89)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - "N-Z" (Box 89)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company (GTLC) - Rungius Paintings (Box 89)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Concessions (Box 89)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company and Subsidiaries - Consolidate Financial Statements, 1983-1984 (Box 89)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company Property Photographs, 2 binders. (Box 89)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Holdings (Box 89)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Finances (Box 89)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Jackson Hole Golf and Tennis Club (Box 89)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company - Meetings/Minutes-, 1982 (Box 89)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company, 1986 June (Box 89)
    Filed as received from GRL
  - Requests - "A-Z" (Box 89)
  - Requests - Wildlife - Wildlands Institute (Box 89)
  - Form CB-86 - Census of Service Industries Membership Organizations, 1977 (Box 90)
  - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Book - Misc. Info (Box 90)
  - Summary Report of the Governor's Conference on Natural Beauty, New York, NY, 1966 February 25 (Box 90)
  - Dams (Box 90)
  - Grand Teton Lodge Company (Box 90)
  - Grunert, Stout and Smock, 1987 (Box 90)
  - Information re: JHPI Brochures (Box 90)